should try others: stand naive bayse, multinomial naive bayse

Most of paper said: use single unigram will give a outstanding result than bigram with / without 
POS. It's weird ?

"The classifier, however, cannot
determine that these four types of good are in any way related, and so in order to train
accurately there must be enough examples of all four in the training corpus"

- Need a preprocessing: lemmatisation 

- Theo 'Alexander Pak and Patrick Paroubek. 2010. Twitter as a corpus for sentiment analysis and opinion mining. In Proceedings of the 7th on International Language Resources and Evaluation Conference (LREC’10). European Language Resources Association (ELRA), 1320–1326.' và 'Giachanou, A., & Crestani, F. (2016). Like it or not: A survey of Twitter sentiment analysis methods. ACM Comput Surv, 49(2), Article 28; 1-41. http://doi.org/10.1145/2938640'
thì càng nhiều dữ liệu, độ chính xác càng tăng

- Thử cls 2 bước, 1 bước tách neutral, 1 bước tách pos và neg